

AYUSH BHATNAGAR

GUEST RELATION EXECUTIVE

PROFILE

I have 3+ years' experience in a busy City Centre Hotel. I have demonstrated exceptional time-management skills, the ability to handle multiple priorities under exceptional customer service to the clients, with a sustained and varied work load most days pressure.

CONTACT

Mob: (+91) 8299766567 / 8874107923

Mail: Ayushihm95@gmail.com Linkedin: https://cutt.ly/nh6y2l4 Address: C-11/3, River Bank Colony, Lucknow, U.P. - 226018

PROJECTS COMPLETED

Successfully completed Industrial Training from "The Hotel Piccadily" Lucknow from 25th January 2015 to 6th May 2016

EXPERIENCE

FEB 2019 - CURRENT

GUEST RELATION EXECUTIVE

Oyo Townhouse 053 | Feb 2019- Present

- Checking guests in and out of the premises.
- Issuing room keys and escorting them to there respected hotels.
- Finalizing bills, collecting payments and providing change.
- Running reports on computer for the team and completing welcoming calls.
- Printing updated in-house, arrival, departure, room status reports every two hours.
- Observing and reporting about damages or security issues to management.

2018

GUEST RELATION EXECUTIVE

The Hotel Legend | Sept 2017 - Dec 2018

- Greeting and welcoming guests to the property.
- Checking guests in and out of the premises.
- Handling a particular shift & reporting about the damages or any issues to the management.
- Verifying the id's and booking and working on them.

2017

GUEST RELATION EXECUTIVE

The Kabila Restaurant | June 2017 - Sept 2017

- Greeting & welcoming guests to the premises.
- Verifying id's and bookings & responding to them.
 Checking online bookings.
- Responding to welcoming calls.
- Providing guests with keys & escorting them to there rooms. Handling particular shift.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR IN HOTEL MANAGEMENT & CATERING TECHNOLOGY, (BHMCT)

IHM Meerut | 2013 - 17

SENIOR SECONDARY SCHOOLING

U.D. Memorial College, Allahabad | 2012 - 2013

SKILLS

Communicational Skills	Team Management
Project Management	Collaborative Nature
Ms - Office	Motivator
Ms - Excel	Leadership
Google Spreadsheets	Tally